

Sagar Maheshwari

Full Stack MERN Developer

sgr.mhshwr22@gmail.com

+918619006139

Beawar, India

sagarm.vercel.app/

linkedin.com/in/sagar-maheshwari- in 3330b6166

github.com/SagarM21 🥊

I'm currently pursuing a degree in B.Tech. focused in Computer Science with a specialization in Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning from the Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal. Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally.

EDUCATION

B.Tech

Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal

10/2020 - Present 8.83

Courses

- CSE (spec. in AI & ML)

Senior Secondary
Kendriya Vidyalaya

05/2017 - 05/2019 Secured 90.2%

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Arishti CyberTech Pvt.Ltd

09/2022 - Present

Arishti (backed by IITB) is building MessageMe™□ - a NextGen Messaging platform for Sensitive Communication using Quantum Technology and AI.

Next.js Developer Doosra College

07/2022 - 08/2022

Remote

- Achievements/Tasks
- Created the whole website from scratch using Next.js.
- Worked with backend developer for making the site functional
- Production of high-quality markup using Tailwind CSS, framer-motion.

Contact : Rishabh Maheshwari

React Developer Froshlink

09/2021 - 12/2021

Remote

- Achievements/Tasks
- Updated the code using NextJS and Typescript.
- Developed new React components for the website which includes the creation of a Resume.
- Produced high-quality markup using HTML, CSS, Material-UI & Tailwind CSS.
- Removed error's related to React.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Jobify (02/2022 - 03/2022)

- Website created to track down the applied jobs, pending jobs easily
- Tech Stack MERN
- GitHub: https://github.com/SagarM21/Jobify

ProShop (07/2021 - 08/2021)

- An e-commerce store created using MERN stack with redux as state management
- Added functionalities like admin dashboard, top page carousel, payment with Paypal, pagination, and cart facility
- GitHub: https://github.com/SagarM21/proShop

DevConnector (06/2021 - 07/2021)

- Social Media for developers, where they can see the profiles of other developers which including their work achievement, their education, etc
- GitHub: https://github.com/SagarM21/DevConnector

CERTIFICATES

Applied Machine Learning in Python (09/2021 - 10/2021)

Learned machine learning concepts and applied them in some projects.

LANGUAGES

Hindi

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency